Trevor Kelly

★ trevork.dev trevor.daniel.kelly@gmail.com TrevorDKelly Pittsburgh, PA

PROFILE

I am a software engineer with multiple years of experience in JavaScript(ES6), Ruby, Go, and various frameworks. I am a cocreator of Chimera \mathscr{O} , which automates canary deployments for containerized microservices that communicate via a service mesh on AWS.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Co-Creator, Software Engineer, Chimera - https://chimera-deploy.dev *⊘*

2022 - present | Remote

An open-source tool for performing automated canary deployments of containerized microservices, allowing software development teams to safely and easily deploy new versions of their code by taking advantage of the features provided by their existing service mesh.

- Automated a deployment process that involves manipulating multiple AWS services concurrently.
- Configured a Cloudwatch agent and Prometheus to monitor traffic flowing through a newly released microservice.
- Automated the rollback process based off of production metrics data.
- Utilized AWS's Software Development Kit to interact with and manipulate cloud infrastructure.
- Created server-sent events stream to pass live updates and metrics data charts to a user interface.
- Built a production microservice system for development testing.
- Designed workflow and infrastructure diagrams.
- Collaborated with a remote team spread across four different cities.
- Authored a comprehensive technical case study documenting design decisions.
- Presented a live tech talk describing the project.

Software Engineer, Self-Employed

2019 - 2022 | Remote

- Monkeys Typing Hamlet Monkey hands randomly typing on a keyboard, tracking whether they type Hamlet.
 - Google Cloud VPS hosted, NGINX reverse proxy, and Node express app with MongoDB and Redis data stores.
- Requestotron Webhook and HTTP request visualizer for viewing and debugging network communication.
 - Node express app with PostgreSQL and MongoDB databases.
- DOM-Keyboard In browser interactive keyboard built out of DOM nodes and released as an npm package.
 - Zero dependency Javascript using promise syntax for chain-able method calls with OOP design.

Operations Manager, Castleview Partners

2016 - 2020 | Chicago

Independent financial advisory firm for high-net-worth individuals

- Transitioned two advisors, over 50 clients, and over 300 accounts to the firm.
- · Organized account set up and management for clients, custodial firms, and private investment companies.

SKILLS

Languages	Frameworks	Technologies	Cloud
Javascript, ES6, Ruby, Go,	Express, Sinatra,	Git, GitHub, Docker, CI/CD,	AWS: ECS, ECR, Fargate,
SQL, HTML, CSS	React/Redux, Node,	HTTP, REST APIs, NGINX,	App Mesh, CloudWatch
	Handlebars, jQuery	Redis, MongoDB	Google Cloud VPS

EDUCATION

Launch School, Software Engineering

2019 - 2022

Multi-year, mastery-based software engineering curriculum with progression gated by written exams and live coding interviews to develop problem-solving skills. Read more at LaunchSchool.com/employers $\mathscr O$